Finding Aid for the CBS Inc. Film and Television Collection PASC-M.0072
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Television Programs, Series 4.
  - Twilight Zone -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 126.
    - The Road Less Traveled, 1986 October 27; 2 in. tape (Box 1013, Folder 1)
      On container, "T.Z./"Road Less Traveled"/10-27-86/R-61B/Reel 61B."
    - The Road Less Traveled, 1986 October 27; 2 in. tape (Box 1013, Folder 2)
      On container, "536/T.Z./Road Less Traveled/10-27-86."
    - Shadow Play, March 29, 1986; 2 in. tape (Box 1036, Folder 4)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/"Shadow Play"/#0059/3-29-86/24 trk/15 IPS."
    - Season 2, episode no. 16: Shelter Skelter. Re-Do's., 1986 November 24; Cassette tape. (Box 1851)
      Music cues: M1, M2. M3, M8.
    - Season 2, episode no.16: Shelter Skelter., 1986 November 16; Cassette tape. (Box 1851)
      Tape case numbered 119.
    - Sounds and Silence, March 11, 1964; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1143, Folder 19)
      On container, "T.Z. 2631/"Sounds And Silence"/3-11-64/."
    - Spur of the Moment, December 11, 1963; open reel audio tape (Box 1058, Folder 9)
      On container, "CBS/prod 2608/"Spur of the moment"/roll #1/12-11-63."
    - The Star, 1985 December 16; 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1647)
      Logs 473-500
    - Still Valley, October 3, 1961; open reel audio tape (Box 1058, Folder 7, Box 3099)
      On container, "Twilight zone/#4808/"Still valley"." CD copy in box 3099
    - Teresa Goldwitz, August 26, 1986; 2 in. tape (Box 968, Folder 2)
      On container, "Has Leaders/499/Twilight Zone "Teresa Goldwitz"/2906-0111/8-26-86/12-48."
    - Tomato Rag, 1986 August 26; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1148, Folder 1)
    - Tomato Rag, 1986 August 26; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1148, Folder 9)
    - Season 2, episode 10: The Toys of Caliban., 1986 November 16; Cassette tape. (Box 1851)
      Container labelled no. 120.
    - What's in the Box?, 1964 January 9; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1156, Folder 4, Box 3099)
      On container, "T.Z./2635/"In The Box"/01-9 64." CD copy in box 3099
    - Season 2, episode 9: World Next Door., Cassette tape. (Box 1851)
      Tape also contains music for Season 2, episode 8, Lost and Found. Evelope containing tape assigns the number 106 to World Next Door.
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1986 January 26; 2 in. tape (Box 971, Folder 1)
      On container, "Music/Reel 2/Hour #16."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1986 January 26; 2 in. tape (Box 971, Folder 5)
      On container, "Music/Reel 1/Hour #16."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1982 September 22; 2 in. tape (Box 972, Folder 1)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/9-22-82/12-55B/Protection/Has Leaders/R-3."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 2 in. tape (Box 975, Folder 2)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/Show #15/R1."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1985 December 9; 2 in. tape (Box 977, Folder 4)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/12-9-85/#0021/Master/R-12A."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1986 January 20; 2 in. tape (Box 978, Folder 2)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/1-20-86/Reel 20B."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1986 January 27; 2 in. tape (Box 978, Folder 3)
      On container, "Twilgiht Zone/#0046/Protection/R-22B."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1985 December 16; 2 in. tape (Box 978, Folder 5)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/12-16-85/#0032/Master/R-14A."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1986 January 27; 2 in. tape (Box 982, Folder 1)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/R23B/1-27-86."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1985 November 11; 2 in. tape (Box 995, Folder 1)
      On container, "The Twilight Zone/11-11-85/R10."
    - [Empty Reel] (Box 996, Folder 1)
      On container, "New Credit Cue (Old)."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1986 September 19; 2 in. tape (Box 1013, Folder 6)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/CBS/9-29-86/Reel 57B."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 2 in. tape (Box 1026, Folder 3)
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1985 December 9; 2 in. tape (Box 1030, Folder 10)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/CBS/12-9-85/Reel 13A."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1986 January 27; 2 in. tape (Box 1030, Folder 11)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/CBS/1-27-86/Reel 23A."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1985 December 16; 2 in. tape (Box 1032, Folder 1)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/R15A/12-16-85."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1986 January 20; 2 in. tape (Box 1032, Folder 3)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/CBS/1-20-86/Reel 21B."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1986 January 20; 2 in. tape (Box 1032, Folder 4)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/CBS/1-20-86/Reel 19B."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1985 December 27; 2 in. tape (Box 1032, Folder 5)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/CBS/12-27-85/Reel 17A."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 7 in., 1/4 in. tape (Box 1034, Folder 16)
      On container, "Twilight Zone #115/Mono Playback."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 7 in., 1/4 in. tape (Box 1034, Folder 17)
      On container, "TZ 101/PB Cues/SC 47-55/Dupe/Reel B."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 7 in., 1/4 in. tape (Box 1034, Folder 18)
      On container, "TZ 101/PB Cues."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1985 December 27; 2 in. tape (Box 1037, Folder 9)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/Reel 2/Show 14/231/R18A."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 7 1/2" reel (Box 1038, Folder 16)
      On container, "Twilight Zone #115/7 1/2 IPS with SMPTE Time Code Center/2 trk/Stereo Nagra."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 7 1/2" reel (Box 1038, Folder 17)
      On container, "Twilight Zone #115/Mono playback/Full track mono with sync 60 cyl.."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1 in. tape (Box 1040, Folder 6)
      On container, "#28/Twilight Zone/Music."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 7" x 1/4" reel (Box 1045, Folder 56)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/#115/Stereo Playback Master."
    - [Contents Unidentified], December 2, 1985; 2 in. tape (Box 1047, Folder 4)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/R9A/12-2-85."
    - [Contents Unidentified], September 13, 1963; open reel audio tape (Box 1058, Folder 4)
      On container, "CBS-TV/Twilight zone/2609/score/9-13-63/Roll #2."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1960 March 7; open reel audio tape (Box 1067, Folder 7)
      On container, "Cayuga Prod./Twilight Zone/#3633/scoring/Long Shot."
    - [Contents Unidentified], August 26, 1986; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1148, Folder 3)
      On container, "T.Z. "Teresa Goldwitz"/"How About You" Piano And Vocal/#2906-0111."
    - [Contents Unidentified], August 26, 1986; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1148, Folder 3)
    - [Contents Unidentified], August 26, 1986; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1148, Folder 7)
      On container, "T.Z. "Teresa Goldwitz"/"How About You" Piano And Vocal, "How About You" Piano Only/#2906-0111."
    - [Title Sequence Music], March 23, 1988; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1149, Folder 2)
      On container, "Opening Title Sequence music: 49 / End Title Sequence Music: 32."
    - [Contents Unidentified], August 26, 1986; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1149, Folder 9)
      On container, "T.Z. "Teresa Goldwitz"/#2906-0111."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1/4 in. tape (Box 1149, Folder 10)
      On container, "Twilight Zone #0101/Elvis "That's All Right" for SC 51."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1/4 in. tape (Box 1149, Folder 11)
      On container, "TZ 101/PB Cues/A-Reel/SC 40A "I Love You Because"/44 "Rag Mop"/51 "That's Alright Ma"/55 "Are You Lonesome Tonight?"."
    - [Contents Unidentified], August 26, 1986; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1149, Folder 14)
      On container, "#2906-0111/T.Z. "Teresa Goldwitz"/"Sweet And Lovely"."
    - Her Pilgrim Soul., Cassette tape (Box 1852)
    - Twilight Zone #0026, Audio Magnetic Film (Box 1875)
      On container, "TR 8, TR 9, TR 10."
    - Twilight Zone #0026, Audio Magnetic Film (Box 1876)
      On container, "TR 11, TR 12, TR 13."
    - Twilight Zone #0026, Audio Magnetic Film (Box 1877)
      On container, "TR 18, TR 19, TR 20."
    - Twilight Zone D418-203, Audio Magnetic Film (Box 1878)
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1 1/2 in. audio magnetic film (Box 3077)
      On container, "Twilight Zone CR A, D422-112, sound, #001."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1 1/2 in. audio magnetic film (Box 3077)
      On container, "Twilight Zone, D423-183."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1 1/2 in. audio magnetic film (Box 3077)
      On container, "Twilight Zone, D423-184."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1 1/2 in. audio magnetic film (Box 3078)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/0001/D419-178/Track"
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1 1/2 in. audio magnetic film (Box 3078)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/001/D422-11/Track"
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1 1/2 in. audio magnetic film (Box 3078)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/0001/D422-177/Track"
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1 1/2 in. audio magnetic film (Box 3079)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/0001/D419-89/Track"
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1 1/2 in. audio magnetic film (Box 3079)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/0001/D419-88/Track"
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1 1/2 in. audio magnetic film (Box 3079)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/0001/D419-176/MAL"
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1 1/2 in. audio magnetic film (Box 3080)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/0001/D419-179/Track"
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1 1/2 in. audio magnetic film (Box 3080)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/0001/426-113/Sound"
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1 1/2 in. audio magnetic film (Box 3080)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/0001/426-115/Sound"
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1 1/2 in. audio magnetic film (Box 3081)
      On container, "Twilight Zone/0001/D426-117/Sound"
  - The United States Steel Hour -- Scores, Subseries 173.
    - Theme (Box 118)
  - The Waltons -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 127.
    Originally called, "The Spencers."
    - Promo, July 28, 1976; open reel audio tape (Box 955, Folder 4)
      On container, "CBS/Waltons Promo/July 28, 76/ Reel 1."
    - Promo, July 28, 1976; 1 in. tape (Box 955, Folder 5)
      On container, "CBS/Walton's Promo/July 28, 76/ Reel 1."
    - The Spencers (logs 161-193), 1976 August 31; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1114, Folder 5)
      On container, "CTN/8-31-76/R9/LOGS 161-193/SP "The Code"."
    - The Spencers (logs 194-227), 1976 August 31; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1114, Folder 6)
      On container, "CTN/8-31-76/R10/LOGS 194-227/SP "The Code"."
  - The Wild Wild West -- Recording Logs, Subseries 128.
    - Broken Record (selection title), 1968 April 23; 1 pages (Box 1771)
      Log 937. Vocal by Ross Martin. Production no. 3224-0601.
    - End Title (new), 1968 July 31; 1 pages (Box 1771)
      Production no. 3224.
    - Logs 414, 417, 423, 433, 613, 616, 619, 628, 630, 666, 668-670, 674, 685, April 30, 1969; 16 p. (Box 1771)
    - Main Title, 1968 July 31; 1 pages (Box 1771)
    - Main Title, 1968 July 31; 1 pages (Box 1771)
    - Main Title, 1968 July 31; 1 pages (Box 1771)
    - Main Title, 1968 July 31; 1 pages (Box 1771)
    - Main Title, 1968 July 31; 1 pages (Box 1771)
    - Play it Fast (selection title), 1968 May 17; 1 pages (Box 1771)
      Log 941. Vocal by Sarita Vara. Production no. 3224-0605.
    - Production no: 1310-3224-9876, 1968 July 31; 2 pages (Box 1771)
      Logs and cues including cue timings and titles, and notes on orchestrations.
    - Season 4, Episode 8: The Night of the Egyptian Queen, 1968 July 15-18; 14 pages (Box 1771)
      Includes cue titles and timings, orchestra size, etc. Production no. 1310-3224-0604.
    - Showcard, 1968 July 31; 2 pages (Box 1771)
    - The Dust (selection title), 1968 May 22; 1 pages (Box 1771)
      Log 939. Vocal by Ross Martin.
    - The Game is Up (selection title), 1968 April 24; 1 pages (Box 1771)
      Log 938. Vocal by Ross Martin. Production no. 3224-0601.
    - The Night of the Deadly Blades (selection title), August 13, 1968; 1 pages (Box 1771)
      Vocal by Ross Martin.
    - Trailer Introduction, 1968 July 31; 1 pages (Box 1771)
    - Trailer Introduction No. 2, 1968 July 31; 1 pages (Box 1771)
    - Episode no. 10: Opening Day, 1985 November 25 (Box 1782)
      The Circle Groove -- On the Boat -- Out There Somewhere -- Who's Closet -- Night of Lust -- River Styx -- Heh, Heh -- Opening Out -- The Dream Journey -- Circle's Party.
    - Episode no. 11: The Beacon, 1985 December 2 (Box 1782)
      Private Property -- Good Medicine -- Atonement -- It Shines.
    - Cue sheets and music clearance documents, 1965-1974 (Box 1827)
    - 1968-1969 Season (Box 1837)
      Includes: names of conductors, composers and arrangers; production numbers; recording dates and locations; episode titles, etc.
  - The Wild Wild West -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 129.
    - Logs 398-417, July 18, 1968; open reel audio tape (Box 931, Folder 8)
      On container, "CBS/7-18-68/R20A/Log 398-417/W.W.W.." Production no. 1310-3224-0604.
    - Logs 418-444, July 18, 1968; open reel audio tape (Box 931, Folder 9)
      On container, "CBS/7-18-68/R21A/Log 418-444/W.W.W.." Production no. 1310-3224-0604.
    - Logs 445-456, July 18, 1968; open reel audio tape (Box 931, Folder 10)
      On container, "CBS/7-18-68/R22A/Log 445-456/W.W.W.." Production no. 1310-3224-0604.
    - Logs 1851-1856, September 29, 1965; open reel audio tape (Box 933, Folder 10)
      On container, "CBS/9-29-65/R81A/Log 1851-1856/Wild West."
    - Logs 1831-1850, September 29, 1965; open reel audio tape (Box 933, Folder 11)
      On container, "CBS/9-29-65/R80A/Log 1831-1850/Wild West."
    - Logs 1641-1667, October 29, 1968; open reel audio tape (Box 946, Folder 7)
      On container, "CBS/76A/Log 1641-1667/Miguelito Revenge."
    - Logs 5873-5905, February 9, 1965; 1/2 in. tape (Box 964, Folder 5)
      On container, "CBS/Wild West/Log 5873-5905/2-9-65 R1/6525/3 Trk Orig."
    - Logs 5906-5936, February 9, 1965; 1/2 in. tape (Box 964, Folder 6)
      On container, "CBS/Wild West/Log 5906-5936/2-9-65 R2/6525/3 Trk Orig."
    - Logs 4260-4265, March 23, 1966; 1/2 in. tape (Box 979, Folder 12)
      On container, "CBS/3-23-66/R1/Log 4260-4265/3S/Wild West."
    - Logs 5233-5283, January 22, 1965; 1/2 in. tape (Box 981, Folder 1)
      On container, "CBCS/Wild West/Log 5233-5283/1-22-65 R1/5123,6525/3 Trk Orig."
    - Logs 5284-5344, January 22, 1965; 1/2 in. tape (Box 981, Folder 2)
      On container, "CBS/Wild West/Log 5284-5344/1-22-65 R2/5123-6525/3 Trk Orig."
    - Logs 5345-5394, January 22, 1965; 1/2 in. tape (Box 981, Folder 3)
      On container, "CBCS/Wild West/Log 5345-5394/1-22-65 R3/5123, 6525/3 Trk Orig."
    - Logs 5427-5448, January 22, 1965; 1/2 in. tape (Box 981, Folder 5)
      On container, "CBS/Wild West/Log 5427-5448/1-22-65 R1/5123 6525/3 Trk Orig."
    - Logs 5427-5448, January 22, 1965; 1/2 in. tape (Box 981, Folder 5)
    - Logs 5449-5480, January 22, 1965; 1/2 in. tape (Box 981, Folder 6)
      On container, "CBS/Wild West/Log 5449-5480/1-22-65 R2/5123 6525/3 Trk Orig."
    - Logs 5449-5480, January 22, 1965; 1/2 in. tape (Box 981, Folder 6)
    - Logs 5481-5519, January 22, 1965; 1/2 in. tape (Box 981, Folder 7)
      On container, "CBS/Wild West/Log 5481-5519/1-22-65 R3/5123 6525/3 Trk Orig."
    - Logs 580-616, June 29, 1966; open reel audio tape (Box 983, Folder 2)
      On container, "CBS/6-29-66/R23B/Log 580-616/W.W.W.."
    - Logs 617-648, June 29, 1965; open reel audio tape (Box 983, Folder 3)
      On container, "CBS/6-29-65/R24B/Log 617-648/W.W.W.."
    - Logs 649-670, June 29, 1966; open reel audio tape (Box 983, Folder 4)
      On container, "CBS/6-29-66/R25B/Log 649-670/W.W.W.."
    - Logs 2671-2690, October 27, 1966; open reel audio tape (Box 983, Folder 15)
      On container, "CBS/10-27-66/R103B/Log 2671-2690/WW."
    - Logs 1669-1694, September 24, 1965; open reel audio tape (Box 983, Folder 17)
      On container, "WW 74A/Log 1669-1694/9-24-65."
    - Logs 1695-1735, September 24, 1965; open reel audio tape (Box 983, Folder 18)
      On container, "WW 75A/Log 1695-1735/9-24-65."
    - Logs 1669-1694, September 24, 1965; open reel audio tape (Box 983, Folder 19)
    - Logs 1736-1764, September 24, 1965; open reel audio tape (Box 983, Folder 19)
      On container, "WW 76A/Log 1736-1764/9-24-65."
    - Logs 2119-2147, October 7, 1965; open reel audio tape (Box 985, Folder 3)
      On container, "CBS/10-7-65/R91A/Log 2119-2147/Wild Wild West."
    - Logs 2148-2172, October 7, 1965; open reel audio tape (Box 985, Folder 4)
      On container, "CBS/10-7-65/R92A/Log 2148-2172/Wild Wild West."
    - Logs 5394-5426, January 22, 1965; 1/2 in. tape (Box 985, Folder 4)
      On container, "CBS/Wild West/Log 5394-5426/1-22-65 R4/5123, 6525/3 Trk Orig."
    - Logs 2173-2186, October 7, 1965; open reel audio tape (Box 985, Folder 5)
      On container, "CBS/10-7-65/R93A/Log 2173-2186/Wild Wild West."
    - Logs 2273-2293, September 22, 1966; open reel audio tape (Box 986, Folder 10)
      On container, "CBS/9-22-66/R85B/Log 2273-2293/WWW."
    - Logs 2294-2320, September 22, 1966; open reel audio tape (Box 986, Folder 11)
      On container, "CBS/9-22-66/R86B/Log 2294-2320/WWW."
    - Logs 2262-2298, October 14, 1965; open reel audio tape (Box 986, Folder 13)
      On container, "CBS/10-14-65/R97A/Log 2262-2298/Wild West."
    - Logs 2299-2316, October 14, 1965; open reel audio tape (Box 986, Folder 14)
      On container, "CBS/10-14-65/R98A/Log 2299-2316/Wild West."
    - Logs 2317-2357, October 14, 1965; open reel audio tape (Box 986, Folder 15)
      On container, "CBS/10-14-65/R99A/Log 2317-2357/Wild West."
    - Logs 2358-2367, October 14, 1965; open reel audio tape (Box 986, Folder 16)
      On container, "CBS/10-14-65/R100A/Log 2358-2367/Wild West."
    - The Night of the Dancing Death, October 22, 1965; open reel audio tape (Box 986, Folder 20)
      On container, "104A/Studio Center/3224-0119/Wild West Dancing Death/10-22-65."
    - Logs 1786-1822, August 24, 1966; open reel audio tape (Box 989, Folder 4)
      On container, "CBS/8-25-66/R67B/Log 1786 to 1822/WWW."
    - Logs 1823-1852, August 25, 1966; open reel audio tape (Box 989, Folder 5)
      On container, "CBS/8-25-66/R68B/Log 1823 to 1852/WWW."
    - Logs 1853-1864, August 25, 1966; open reel audio tape (Box 989, Folder 6)
      On container, "CBS/8-25-66/R69B/Log 1853 to 1864/WWW."
    - Logs 2834-2839, November 11, 1965; open reel audio tape (Box 990, Folder 1)
      On container, "CBS/11-11-65/R119A/Log 2834-2839/Wild Wild West."
    - Logs 2813-2833, November 11, 1965; open reel audio tape (Box 990, Folder 11)
      On container, "CBS/Log 2813-2833/R118A/Wild West/11-11-69."
    - Logs 2001-2026, September 6, 1966; open reel audio tape (Box 990, Folder 14)
      On container, "CBS/9-6-66/Log 2001-2026/WWW."
    - Logs 2027-2060, September 6, 1966; open reel audio tape (Box 990, Folder 15)
      On container, "CBS/9-6-66/Log 2027-2060/WWW."
    - Logs 2061-2073, September 6, 1966; open reel audio tape (Box 990, Folder 16)
      On container, "CBS/9-6-66/Log 2061-2073/WWW."
    - The Night of the Dancing Death, October 22, 1965; open reel audio tape (Box 992, Folder 10)
      On container, "Studio Center/3224-0118 Wild West/Dancing Death/10-22-65."
    - Logs 2716-2746, November 3, 1965; open reel audio tape (Box 992, Folder 20)
      On container, "CBS/11-3-65/R114A/Log 2716-1746/Wild West."
    - Logs 1298-1322, 1967 September 18; open reel audio tape (Box 1001, Folder 4)
      On container, "CBS/WWW 0361/R58A/Log 1298-1322/9-18-67."
    - Logs 1283-1297, 1967 September 18; open reel audio tape (Box 1001, Folder 19)
      On container, "CBS/WWW 0361/R57A/Log 1283-1297/9-18-67."
    - Logs 894-906, July 18, 1966; open reel audio tape (Box 1002, Folder 13)
      On container, "CBS/7-18-66/R35B/Log 894-906/W.W.."
    - Logs 854-895, July 18, 1966; open reel audio tape (Box 1002, Folder 14)
      On container, "CBS/7-18-66/R34B/Log 854-895/W.W.."
    - Logs 820-850, July 18, 1966; open reel audio tape (Box 1002, Folder 15)
      On container, "CBS/7-18-66/R33B/Log 820-850/W.W.."
    - Logs 2243-2271, February 4, 1969; open reel audio tape (Box 1006, Folder 4)
      On container, "CBS/2-4-69/R101A Close Shot/Logs 2243-2271/WW "Diva"."
    - Logs 1-8, July 12, 1965; open reel audio tape (Box 1031, Folder 13)
      On container, "CBS/7-12-65/R13A/Log 001-008/Wild West."
    - Logs 3778-3781, August 12, 1966; open reel audio tape (Box 1041, Folder 2)
      On container, "CBS/8-12-66/R59B/Log 3778-3781/Wild West."
    - Logs 1409-1441, August 11, 1966; open reel audio tape (Box 1041, Folder 12)
      On container, "8-11-66/R55B/Log 1409-1441/WWW."
    - Logs 1448-1473, August 11, 1966; open reel audio tape (Box 1043, Folder 4)
      On container, "CBS/8-11-66/R56A/Log 1448-1473/WWW."
    - Logs 3769-3777, August 12, 1966; open reel audio tape (Box 1043, Folder 6)
      On container, "CBS/8-12-66/R58B/Log 3769-3777/Wild Wild West."
    - The Night of the Iron Fist, January 18, 1968; open reel audio tape (Box 1098, Folder 13)
      On container, "CBS/1-18-68/R95A/TK1/WW-Iron Fist/Payback."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1999 October 18; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1145, Folder 18)
      On container, "CED/R34/"Jesu" + Verdi "Tacea La Notte"/"Blood River" (Wm Goldstein) PS."
    - The Night of the Cutthroats, 1/4 in. tape (Box 1153, Folder 12)
      On container, "Wild Wild West/Show 0353 "Cut Throats"/Reel 5 + 6/Music Only."
    - The Night of the Running Death, [1967]; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1155, Folder 1)
      On container, "Wild Wild West/Music R4/0364/Wild Wild (No Sync)/"Running Death"/67-68."
  - Wildfire -- Papers, Subseries 130.
    - Note To Editors -- Saturday Mornings on CBS, 1986 November 11; 1 p. (Box 1859, Folder 11)
      A note about the continued production of the Hanna-Barbera Studios program "Wildfire," developed with Peter S. Beagle, author of "The Last Unicorn." Score by the well-known Jimmy Webb.
  - You Take the Kids -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 131.
    - You Take The Kids., 1990 November 18; Cassette tape (Box 1852)
      Score.
  - Miscellaneous TV Programs -- Scores, Subseries 182.
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 150)
      Foreign Library: folders 0001-0999.
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 151)
      Foreign Library: folders 1000-1999
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 152)
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 152)
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 153)
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 154)
      Foreign Library: folders 2000-2999
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 155)
      Foreign Library: folders 1-12
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 156)
      Foreign Library: folders 13-45
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 157)
      Foreign Library: folders 46-69
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 158)
      Foreign Library: folders 70-186
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 159)
      Foreign Library: folders 200-299
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 160)
      Foreign Library: folders 300-999
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 161)
      Foreign Library: folders 4000-4199
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 162)
      Foreign Library: folders 4200-4399
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 163)
      Foreign Library: folders 4400-4499
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 164)
      Foreign Library: folders 4500-4599
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 165)
      Foreign Library: folders 4600-4899
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 166)
      Foreign Library: folders 3000's
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 167)
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 168)
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 169)
      Foreign Library: folders 3500-3900
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 170)
      Foreign Library: folders 3101-3570
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 171)
      Foreign Library: folders 3841-3990
    - Miscellaneous scores, ozalid (Box 172)
      Foreign Library: folders 3100-3600
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 174)
      Foreign Library: folders 5000's
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 175)
      Foreign Library: folders 5317-5398
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 176)
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 179)
      Foreign Library: folders 6062-6161
    - Miscellaneous scores (Box 180)
      Foreign Library: folders 6166-6221